{
  "\u0422\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0441\u043f\u043e\u0440\u0442": {
    "100": {
      "question": "plane",
      "answer": "\u0441\u0430\u043c\u043e\u043b\u0435\u0442",
      "asked": false
    },
    "200": {
      "question": "train",
      "answer": "\u043f\u043e\u0435\u0437\u0434",
      "asked": false
    },
    "300": {
      "question": "boarding",
      "answer": "\u043f\u043e\u0441\u0430\u0434\u043a\u0430",
      "asked": false
    }
  },
  "\u0416\u0438\u0432\u043e\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0435": {
    "100": {
      "question": "dog",
      "answer": "\u0441\u043e\u0431\u0430\u043a\u0430",
      "asked": false
    },
    "200": {
      "question": "shark",
      "answer": "\u0430\u043a\u0443\u043b\u0430",
      "asked": false
    },
    "300": {
      "question": "sparrow",
      "answer": "\u0432\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0439",
      "asked": false
    },
    "400": {
      "question": "sparrow",
      "answer": "\u0432\u043e\u0440\u043e\u0431\u0435\u0439",
      "asked": false
    }
  },
  "\u0424\u0440\u0443\u043a\u0442\u044b": {
    "100": {
      "question": "aplle",
      "answer": "\u044f\u0431\u043b\u043e\u043a\u043e",
      "asked": false
    },
    "200": {
      "question": "berry",
      "answer": "\u044f\u0433\u043e\u0434\u0430",
      "asked": false
    },
    "300": {
      "question": "vension",
      "answer": "\u043e\u043b\u0435\u043d\u0438\u043d\u0430",
      "asked": false
    }
  }
}